tips4pc.com 2009-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site and this [Forum](http://www.pctipforum.com/). If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information  
**We do not collect personally identifiable information like names and postal addresses. The only information we collect is an email address when you sign up for the free newsletter. Also any information shared by a user of this website within the forum is for public view, therefore you should be aware of what information you are giving out. 

**Distribution of Information**  
We do not share information with any other companies. The collection of your email address is to send a monthly newsletter showing updates and new articles on our website. We will never sell or distribute your email address. Our mailing list is managed by a professional company to ensure top security. 

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your email address is kept securely on a third party professional email manage website. Only authorized employees, (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. 

**Opting Out**

All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. We will not make it difficult to unsubscribe.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies on this website. It is only used for internet traffic statistics.  We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Links to other Websites or Paid advertising**  
Our website may contain links to other relevant sites. They may be ads from Google Adsense or from other computer related sites. However when you click on these links or ads this privacy policy no longer applies as you are no longer at this site. If you are providing personal information on a website it is recommended that you read their privacy policy. 

**Free Computer Help Offer**  
Our website offers free computer help, tips, and video tutorials, that have 99% of the time been tested and work. However we cannot take any responsibility for the damage you may cause to your computer while following instructions from this website. The information is provided free and is yours to use at your own risk. 

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us for more information.  

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

Browse Sitemap for more Free Computer Help
